http://www.hammertap.com/privacy_policies

HammerTap Privacy Policy
We are commited to your privacy!
Your privacy is important, so we'd like to explain what information we collect when you visit this web site or use the services provided, why we collect it and how it is used. We'd also like to explain your options to access and control your information, our data security practices and other matters.
In the course of serving its customers, HammerTap acquires, stores and transmits customer communications and information that customers may regard as private or sensitive. Some of this information - such as the customer’s name, address, telephone number, and credit card data - is provided to HammerTap by its customers in order to establish service. Other information - such as the customer’s account status, choice of services, and customer logs - is created and maintained by HammerTap in the normal course of providing service. HammerTap also uses cookies, which are small pieces of information that a web site can store in a designated file on a user’s computer for various reasons. For example, HammerTap uses cookies on the landing pages of products sold online which record the customer information that is required on the order form. This information is then forwarded to an internal sales tracking database within HammerTap. In addition, HammerTap may store customers’ electronic mail and other communications as a necessary incident to the transmission and delivery of those communications.
This Privacy Policy applies only to HammerTap's treatment of data collected online, and does not apply to any offline data collection practices or to the data collection practices of any third parties, HammerTap customers, or any entities affiliated with HammerTap. Also, please note that use of HammerTap's website constitutes acceptance of this Privacy Policy.
HammerTap's policies and procedures for handling customer information have been created with the understanding that Internet technologies are still evolving and that Internet business methods are continuing to evolve to meet the needs and opportunities of the changing technologies. As a result, HammerTap's policies and procedures are subject to change. Changes will be posted to the website and use of HammerTap's website will constitute acceptance of and agreement to be bound by those changes.
Data Security
HammerTap protects the confidentiality of its customers’ information, account information and personal communications. To secure the information collected online, prevent unauthorized access, maintain data accuracy and ensure only appropriate use of information that is collected from customers, HammerTap has implemented appropriate physical, electronic, and managerial procedures. Further, HammerTap requires that employees keep customer information confidential. HammerTap cautions its customers and website visitors that no medium of communication, including the Internet, is entirely secure. Accordingly, HammerTap cannot be responsible for loss, corruption or unauthorized acquisition and use of personal information provided to our website, or for any damages resulting from such loss, corruption, unauthorized acquisition or unauthorized use.
How is customer information used?
HammerTap may share customer information with selected partners, for example, to provide customers with information about products which might be of interest to the customer or to enable the customer to take advantage of special partner programs. HammerTap may also use customer information to provide its customers with system information or information about new or upgraded products. In addition, HammerTap may collect and share non personally identifiable information (such as website usage information) from visitors to its web sites with third-party companies for various purposes such as statistical analysis, performance optimization and promotional uses. In the case of a business transaction, including but not limited to, a merger or sale of a portion of HammerTap's assets, customer information will likely be part of the assets transferred. In this event, HammerTap will attempt to notify impacted customers that their information has been transferred.
Any information you provide to HammerTap may be combined with information from other sources and used by HammerTap, or a third party retained by HammerTap, to help detect and prevent fraud, misuse of HammerTap's website or other illegal activity.
Parts or all of this information may be retained by us or the third parties involved in fraud detection and used for future fraud prevention efforts.
Information believed to be fraudulent may be shared with other merchants, banks and law enforcement officials to help prevent further misuse.
HammerTap may also use "device identification" technology to recognize specific computers or other internet devices each time they access the website, and associate historical data with that computer or device as part of its efforts to prevent fraud or other misuse.
Modifications
Customers may not opt out of receiving information from HammerTap that is essential for maintaining or updating customers’ accounts or system information.
Most customers may access and modify their personal information via their online personal Executive Suite page. All other customers may access and modify their personal information by contacting the appropriate HammerTap Billing organization.
Disclosure of customer information and communications
HammerTap will not otherwise disclose its customers’ personal and account information unless HammerTap has reason to believe that disclosing such information is necessary to identify, make contact with, or bring legal action against someone who may be causing harm or interfering with the rights or property of HammerTap, HammerTap's customers, or others, or where HammerTap has a good faith belief that the law requires such disclosure such as in response to legal process seeking disclosure of such information.
HammerTap also will not, except for reasons stated below, disclose to third parties the contents of any electronic mail or other electronic communications that HammerTap stores or transmits for its customers. The circumstances under which HammerTap will disclose such electronic customer communications are when:
it is necessary in order to provide service to the customer;
it is necessary to protect the legitimate interests of HammerTap and its customers;
it is required to cooperate with interception orders, warrants, or other legal process that HammerTap determines in its sole discretion to be valid and enforceable; and
it is necessary to provide to a law enforcement agency when the contents are inadvertently obtained by HammerTap and appear to pertain to the commission of a crime.
This Site operates AS-IS and AS-AVAILABLE, without liability of any kind. HammerTap disclaims any intention to censor, edit or engage in ongoing review or surveillance of communications stored on or transmitted through its facilities by customers or others. HammerTap, however, may review, delete or block access to communications that may harm HammerTap, its customers or third parties. The grounds on which HammerTap may take such action include, but are not limited to, actual or potential violations of HammerTap's Acceptable Use Policy.
Last Modified October 9, 2010
About Us ·
Contact Us ·
Free Newsletter ·
Privacy Policy ·
Support ·
Site Map
©2010 HammerTap
